A Guide to the Friends of Virginia Libraries records, 1986, 1993-2001
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Friends of Virginia Libraries records, 1986, 1993-2001
The Library of Virginia
51436
.525 cubic feet (2 boxes)
Friends of Virginia Libraries
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred.
Scope and Content
Records, 1986, 1993-2001, of the Friends of Virginia Libraries containing agendas, brochures, bylaws, clippings, constitution, directories, emails, fliers,letters, memorandums, newsletters, notes, photographs, and other papers detailing the organization and operation of the Friends of the Virginia Libraries to support public libraries throughout the state.
Contents List
- Directory and activities, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Organizational meeting, 10 September 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Papers, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Papers, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Papers, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Papers, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Papers, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Papers, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 5th annual meeting, 15 May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Surveys, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Papers, January-March 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Papers, April-June 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 6th annual meeting, 7 May 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 6th annual meeting photographs, 7 May 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Papers, July-December, no date, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Papers, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 7th annual meeting, 5 May 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Papers, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
- The Illuminated newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- The Illuminated newsletter, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Illuminated newsletter, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- The Illuminated newsletter, 1990-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Friends of the Caroline Public Library, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Friends of the Chesterfield Public Library, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Friends of Essex Public Library, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Friends of the Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1998, no date (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Friends of the Richmond Public Library, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Friends of the Washington County Public Library, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Regional meetings of library friends, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Friends of Libraries USA papers, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Friends of Libraries USA news update, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Friends of Libraries USA fact sheets 1, 3-7, 11b-19, 21-22 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Non-Virginia friends of library organizations, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Virginia public libraries (Augusta, Bedford, Chesterfield, and Mathews Counties), 1999, no date (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Library of Virginia newsletters, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Virginia Foundation for the Humanities (Virginia Humanities), 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Advertisements, catalogs, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)